Lesley Pond

Email: lesley.pond@gmail.com | Phone: 919-633-5388 | Durham, NC 27704

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lesley-pond-484343174/| Github: https://github.com/LesleyPond|

Website: https://lesleypond.github.io/

SUMMARY

Front-End Developer with excellent interpersonal skills and ten plus years of customer service experience. Independent musician with extensive knowledge of video and audio editing. Passionate about UI/UX. Attendee of UNC Coding Bootcamp. Currently studying Node.js and MySQL.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML/CSS | Javascript | JQuery | Video Editing | Audio Editing | Node.js | Bootstrap | APIs | Moment.js | Git | Github | mySQL | Materialize |

PROJECTS

BukNuk | https://github.com/LesleyPond/BukNuk | https://hankatola.github.io/BukNuk

A locale-based reading app to store and add favorite books, and see other user's data in your area...

- Designed concept and app aesthetic.
- Led firebase implementation and authorization. Edited/debugged Javascript and layout.
- Firebase, HTML/CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap

An auto-updating scheduling app implementing Javascript, Moment.js, jQuery. Firebase authentication and Bootstrap tables.

Trivia Game | https://github.com/LesleyPond/trivia-game|https://lesleypond.github.io/trivia-game/
A timer-based trivia game using gifs, timeouts, Javascript, jQuery, and Bootstrap.

Gif-tastic | https://github.com/LesleyPond/gifTastic | https://lesleypond.github.io/gifTastic/ A fun gif-search engine implementing API calls, local storage, jQuery and Bootstrap

EXPERIENCE

<u>Lead Bartender</u> – *Dain's Place* – Durham, NC

2011 - Present

Senior staff member responsible for training new employees and oversight of nightly operations.

Key Responsibilities:

- Training and mentoring new and currently staff
- Creating and implementing daily specials and new featured cocktails
- Handling operational procedures such as deposits, order generation, intake and payment.

<u>Music Producer and Performer</u> – Durham, NC **2012 - 2018**

Award-winning independent musician

Key Achievements:

- Indaba Music Award winner 2015 & 2016
- Music featured in Xbox video game
- Self-recorded, mixed and mastered multiple releases
- Recorded and directed multiple music videos for various artists

<u>Assistant Salon/Spa Manager</u> – Aveda Institute of Chapel Hill, NC **2009 - 2011**

Retail and sales manager with additional duties in inventory control

Key Achievements:

- Implemented individual staff sales tracking formulas and employee sales guide
- Created student sales incentives and awards
- Implemented inventory tracking of retail and salon areas
- Created weekly orders for 200+ student salon and retail area

EDUCATION

UNC, Chapel Hill, NC – Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp North Carolina State University – B.A Psychology, 3.9 GPA